eshopworld.com 2011-01-26

# Privacy policy – eShopWorld

We are committed to protecting your privacy and this page outlines our policy concerning your personal information. By using the eShopWorld website, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We comply with the principles of the EU Data Protection Directive (EU 95/46) and other regional equivalents and aim to maintain consistently high levels of best practice in the processing of your personal data.

### What information do we collect?

eShopWorld collects the details provided by you when you order or register on our site. We also collect information about the transactions you undertake including details of payment cards used. Information we collect from you may be used in one or more of the following ways:

  1. To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  2. To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  3. To improve our customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

### How do we protect your information?

We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of customer information. All sensitive credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. SSL is the industry standard method of encrypting personal information and credit/debit card details so that they can be securely transferred over the internet.

### Do we use Cookies?

Yes, this site uses cookies. Cookies are pieces of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect certain information from the browser. eShopWorld uses cookies for a number of purposes, for instance to enable us to simplify the logging on process for registered users, to help ensure the security and authenticity of registered users, to provide the mechanisms for online shopping and to enable traffic monitoring. While you do not need to allow your browser to accept cookies, you must have cookies enabled in order to browse much of our website or to shop online at any of our partner stores.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information (except for any successors in title to our business). This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

### Third Party links

This Privacy Policy only covers websites that we own and control. Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from our own. 

We are not responsible for the privacy policy of other websites.

### Terms of Use

Our Terms of Use can be found by clicking on this link Terms of Use

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at anytime. Any changes made will be updated on our website.

### Access Rights

You have the right at any time to access the personal data that we hold about you by furnishing us with a written request. There is no fee for providing this information. We are concerned to ensure that at all times such personal data as we hold about you, is accurate, up to date and is not in excess of what we require to enable you to avail of our services. Therefore, if your personal information changes, or indeed if you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please let us know and we will correct, update or delete your personal data as appropriate. This can be done by emailing us at info@eshopworld.com or by post to

eShopWorld,  
41 Dogwood Road,  
Asheville,  
NC 28806.
